getridofthings.com 2016-11-25

# Privacy - GETRIDOFTHiNGS.COM

  * ARTICLES

## A do-it-yourself guide for getting rid of just about anything.

Saint Paul Media, Inc. (SPM) websites, including GetRidofThings.com (GROT), are governed by the following privacy policy.

## INTRODUCTION

SPM respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it. This Privacy Policy is intended to inform you of our Privacy Policy and of the choices you can make about the way your information is collected online and how that information is utilized by us.

Certain pages on our website have been structured so that you can access the GROT website without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information. However, should you wish to make full use of the GROT website you will be required to register and provide us with personal information; accordingly, we have made this notice readily available on our homepage and at the bottom of every page that collects personal information.

## APPLICABILITY

This Privacy Policy applies to the GROT websites only. This statement is not applicable to other related websites not specifically included.

The GROT websites may contain links to or from other sites (“linked sites”), including sites maintained by SPM but which are not governed by this Privacy Policy. Accordingly, SPM is in no way responsible for the content or the privacy and security policies employed by linked sites.

## TYPES OF INFORMATION COLLECTED

When you register on the GROT website we need to collect certain information about you in order to provide you with the services you have requested. This information may include, but is not limited to:

Name  
Email Address  
Other biographic information you choose to share.

Once you choose to register with GROT and provide us with personal information, it will be used for the purposes of providing you with the requested service. We respect your privacy and undertake not to sell, rent or lease your personal information to others.

Certain non-personal information may be collected while you are using the website. This will comprise of data about usage and service operation that is not associated with a specific personal identity. SPM may collect and use this non-personal information to evaluate how the GROT websites are being used.

Most non-personal data is collected via cookies or other analysis technologies. The GROT website pages use anonymous cookies and other technologies for data analysis and potential personalization of the website and services offered.

These technologies may vary, but in many cases may involve a small file stored locally on the computer used to access the GROT websites, and may be used to store and collect information relating to your viewing and use of the websites. Information collected through cookies is used to create a profile of our users. A profile is stored information we keep on individual users that details their preferences, their use and request history and behavioral activity, and can minimize the need for you to re-enter information.

Most cookies expire after a defined period of time, or you can delete your cookie file at any time. Most web browser software is initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your web browser software to refuse cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some parts of our Site will not function properly or may be considerably slower if you refuse cookies. For example, without cookies, you will not be able to set personalized preferences, and/or may have difficulty completing transactions.

SPM may collect your computer’s IP (Internet Protocol) address and domain name address, the identity of your Internet service or access provider, the type of web browsing software you use, your computer’s operating system, the URL of the web page from which you came to visit our Site and the language you selected for your web browsing software (collectively referred to herein as clickstream data). We use these technologies to identify our users, to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer the GROT websites and the services offered thereon.

SPM needs and uses your personal information to provide you with the services you request and to help us better understand your needs and interests in the future. Specifically, SPM uses your information to help you complete and process the transactions you have requested. Sensitive personal information if collected will only be used if you choose to allow us to do this in terms of your personal preferences options and will be shared only with your express permission.

Personal data given to SPM may be transferred across state and country borders for the purposes of data consolidation, storage and simplified customer information management.

HOW SPM WILL SHARE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION AND WITH WHOM  
SPM will not share your personal information with third parties except in responding to your requests for products or services. Your permission will be requested when you submit your information.

SPM and partners, who may provide you with the services requested through the GROT websites, are required to keep confidential the information received on behalf of SPM and may not use it for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for your experience on GROT. SPM will not share personal information with any other third parties without your permission, unless required by law enforcement action, subpoena, or local law.

GROT or SPM’S other websites could merge with or be acquired by another business entity or organization. In that event SPM will make every reasonable effort to notify you in the event we share with the merging or acquiring entity some or all of your personal information. However, you are requested to continually check this Privacy Policy for any updates or changes.

## COLLECTION OF INFORMATION BY THIRD PARTIES

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to deliver (or “serve”) the advertisements and links that appear on GROT directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see. SPM has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the Google ad and content network privacy policy at this link for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt out of certain practices. SPM’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

## DATA ACCESS, ACCURACY, AMENDMENTS, RETENTION, AND OPTING OUT

SPM will try to keep your personal information accurate. We will provide you with access to your information, including making reasonable efforts to provide you with online access and the opportunity to change your information, if possible. To protect your privacy and security, when doing so we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity, such as a password and user ID, before granting access to your data.

## UPON REQUEST, SPM WILL:

Correct personal information that you state is incorrect; or  
Permit you to opt out of further contact (excepting notification of major changes to the service), either on the original site of registration or at any time subsequently, while still allowing basic access to the site;  
Remove you and your personal information provided electronically from our database, thereby canceling your registration.

To request a correction or cancellation, send an email to staff@getridofthings.com.

## SECURITY

SPM undertakes to take all reasonable measures to protect the information you provide us. These measures include, but are not limited to: preventing unauthorized access or disclosure, maintaining data accuracy, and ensuring the appropriate use of the information. SPM has in place appropriate physical and managerial procedures to safeguard the information we collect.

You must protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Please sign off when you have finished using a shared computer. Your emails to us are not necessarily secure against interception, so do not include sensitive information in them. We will not ask for passwords in an email and you should assume that if you get such a request, it might be fraudulent. You must do what you reasonably can to ensure the security of your personal information.

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily provide information in public areas of the GROT websites, that information can be viewed and possibly used by others. We therefore advise users not to disclose contact information, including phone number, email address, street address, or instant messenger address (within these public areas) that they do not wish to share. We are not responsible for personally identifying information you choose to submit in these public areas.

## CHANGES TO THIS STATEMENT

Please note that these guidelines are subject to change at any time. Any such changes will be posted on this page. You are encouraged to review this Privacy Policy at the inception of each session.

## ACCEPTANCE OF POLICY

By using the GROT websites, or otherwise providing your personal information to Saint Paul Media, Inc., you signify your acceptance of our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use the websites or provide any personal information to Saint Paul Media, Inc.
